怎么回事  森林惹到你了
So what happened? Did a forest tick you off?
不  我们不一直说要个信箱嘛
No. Y'know how we're always saying we need a place for the mail.
然后呢
Yeah!
然后我就开工啦
I started building one.
不过呢  我决定更上一层楼
But then I decided to take it to the next step.
你要盖邮局
You're building a post office?
不  是娱乐专用柜  内嵌信箱
No, an entertainment unit, with a mail cubby built right in.
最多一天完工
It's a one-day job, max.
好吧
OK.
天呐  你还穿上紧身裤了
My word, those are snug!
是啊  这是我的旧工作裤
Oh yeah. These are my old work pants.
"亚曼范伦铁"牌的
Sergio Valente.
刚才电锯有点失控
Power saw kind of got away from me there.
菲比  你弟出现了吗
Hey, Pheebs. Any sign of your brother?
还没  不过他老是迟到
No, but he's always late.
-你不是只见过他一次嘛  -是啊
- I thought you only met him once. - Yeah, I did.
这样讲比较有姐姐的派头嘛
I think it sounds like, you know, big sister-y, you know,
'法兰克老是迟到"
"Frank's always late."
别急  他会来的
Well, relax. He'll be here.
我知道  我只是紧张而已
No, I know. I'm just nervous.
我老妈死了  我也不和我姐说话
Y'know it's just y'know Mom's dead, don't talk to my sister...
奶奶最近整天睡觉
...Grandma's been sleeping a lot lately.
这是可算是
It's just the "last-desperate-chance-
我拥有家人的最后机会
to-have-a-family" you know, kind of thing.
你陪我等真好
You're so sweet to wait with me.
是甘瑟叫我来的
Well, actually Gunther sent me.
杯子不能拿出来
You're not allowed to have cups out here.
还有谁觉得大卫·考柏菲长得可爱
Does anyone else think David Copperfield's cute?
没有  不过他告诉我  他觉得你很性感
No. But he told me he thinks you're a fox.
珍妮丝喜欢他
All right. Janice likes him.
喜欢到把他放进她的"爱爱"名单里
In fact, she likes him so much, she put him on her "freebie" list.
什么名单
Her what?
我们说好
We have a deal
每人可以挑五个名人上床
where we each pick five celebrities we could sleep with...
而另一个人不准生气
...and the other one can't get mad.
这是健康恋爱关系的核心
The heart of every healthy relationship:
诚实  尊重  与名人上床
Honesty, respect and sex with celebrities.
钱德勒  你的名单里有谁?
So Chandler, who's on your list?
金·贝辛格
Ah, Kim Basinger...
辛蒂·克劳馥  荷莉·贝瑞
Cindy Crawford, Halle Berry...
雅丝敏·布丽丝
Yasmine Bleeth...
和罗杰兔的老婆洁西卡
and Jessica Rabbit.
你知道她是卡通人物  跟你不合适吧
Now, You do realize that she is a cartoon, and way out of your league?
我知道  我是好奇
I know. I know. I just wonder
自己能不能让她的眼珠掉出来
if I could get her eyes to pop out of her head.
莫妮卡  你会选谁
Hey, Monica, who would yours be?
我得先交男朋友  才能列名单
First, I need a boyfriend. Then I can have a list.
说着玩而已  莫妮卡
It's a game, Mon.
瑞秋  你呢
Rach, how about you?
不知道啦
I don't know.
或许是克里斯·欧唐纳  小约翰·甘乃迪
I guess Chris O'Donnell,John F.Kennedy Jr...
丹尼尔·戴路易斯  史汀和帕克·史蒂文生
Daniel Day-Lewis,Sting and Parker Stevenson.
《蜘蛛侠》里的
Spiderman?
是《硬汉子》里的
Hardy Boy.
-《蜘蛛侠》那是彼得·帕克  -谢谢
- Peter Parker. - Thank you.
你呢亲爱的  你会选谁
What about you, honey? Who'd be on your list?
这种事需要深思熟虑
I, well, that kind of thing requires some serious thought.
我会先把候选人归归类
First, I'll divide my perspective candidates into categories.
书呆子
What a geek!
各位这是法兰克  我同父异母的弟弟
Everybody, this is Frank! This is my half brother, Frank!
就是他们
This is everybody.
-这是罗斯  -你好
- This is Ross. - How are you?
钱德勒
Chandler.
乔伊
Joey.
这是莫妮卡
This is Monica.
这是瑞秋
And this is Rachel.
我去拿几杯咖啡
I'm gonna get coffee for us.
你们几个是怎么走到一起的
Hey, how do you guys get anything done?
我们其实没在一起
We don't really.
你们有什么安排吗
So now, do you guys have a lot of big plans?
当然啦  我们要好好的联络感情
Oh,yeah yeah. We're gonna connect and bond and everything.
我觉得我们可以去时代广场
Yeah, I was thinking we could go down to Times Square
买几个忍者娃娃
and pick up some ninja stars.
我朋友赖瑞托我拍张妓女的照片
Oh, oh, my friend, Larry, he wants me to take a picture of a hooker.
我们在纽约都白住了
You know, we really don't take advantage of living in the city.
抱歉  我钻到你了吗
Oh, sorry. Did I get you?
不  你没有钻到我
No, you didn't "get" me!
这可是电钻
It's an electric drill!
你要是钻到我  我就死定了
You "get" me, you kill me!
别激动  你到底要不要这个柜子嘛
Calm down! Do you want this unit or not?
我不要这个柜子
I do not want this unit!
你不早说  我又不会心电感应
You should've told me that before. Not a mind reader.
没有啤酒了  我要去莫妮卡那
And we're out of beer. Okay, I'm going to Monica's.
好极了
Fine!
你穿成这样要去哪  回到1982年吗
Hey, Where you heading in those pants? 1982?
对了莫妮卡  我在装潢建材店看到
Oh, Monica, listen. I saw down at the hardware store,
品牌瓷砖在打折
they got those designer tiles on sale...
如果你想要重铺浴室地砖的话
...if you wanna redo your bathroom floor.
我的浴室地砖怎么了
What's wrong with my bathroom floor?
没什么  又旧又脏而已
Nothing. It's just old and dingy, that's all.
没有这回事
I highly doubt that.
你把桶子移开
Oh yeah. If you move your hamper...
就可以看到瓷砖原来的颜色
...you see the color of the tile used to be.
这种地方我怎么住
I can't live like this!
我们该怎么办  这下怎么办
What are we gonna do? What are we gonna do?
别激动  拿着
Relax. Here, hold this.
瓷砖一撬就掉了  我弄给你看
This old stuff comes right up. I'll show you.
我可没想让你撬
A little more than I wanted to see.
你看看  粘得多死啊
Look at that! Every inch of this is glued down!
得撬到什么时候啊  我看你就将就着吧
It'd take forever to pry this up. You should just leave it.
这怎么将就
I can't leave it!
你在我又脏又旧的地板上撬了个洞
You gouged a hole in my dingy floor!
这样就好了
There. There you go.
挺和谐的
Yeah, that's nice.
倒不如就先塞进
You know, we can put it back there
你菊花里算了
after the surgeons remove it from your colon!
干嘛
What?
我知道要问什么了  你会卷舌头吗
Yeah I know what I wanted to ask you. Can you roll your tongue?
因为我会  但是我妈不会
Because I can and my mom couldn't, and I thought you know.
我想那一定受到了爸爸的遗传
And I figured that was something I got from our dad.
等等  你是说这样
What, wait, you mean like this?
对  你也会啊
Yeah, you can do it too. Yeah.
你没有卷啊
You're not doing it.
好吧  所以是我妈会  而我不会
Oh, right. Okay. Yeah, my mom could and I can't.
我们这一点不同
We don't have that.
你的生日是哪一天
When's your birthday?
2月16日
February 16th.
我认识一个18号生的人
I know a guy who's the 18th.
蛮近的
That's close.
你的生日呢
When's yours?
10月25日
October 25th.
跟万圣节在同一个月
That's the same month as Halloween.
你在家里喜欢做什么
So what kind of things do you like to do at home?
烧东西
Melt stuff.
-好  我已经挑了三个  -三个什么
- Okay, I've got three of my five. - Three of your five what?
可以上床的名人
Celebrities I'm allowed to sleep with.
天哪  你还真是深思熟虑啊
Oh, my God, you're giving this a lot of thought.
很难挑的好吗  我只剩两个空缺了
Hey, it's hard, okay? I only have two spots left.
你都选出谁了
All right. Who you got it narrowed down to?
伊丽莎白·赫莉
Elizabeth Hurley.
大美女
Very attractive.
值得原谅
Forgiving.
苏珊·莎兰登
Susan Sarandon.
她太热衷政治了
You know what? She's too political.
她答应跟你上床前
she probably wouldn't let you do it,
可能会叫你先捐四个罐头
unless you donated four cans of food first.
还有伊莎贝拉·罗塞里尼
And Isabella Rossellini.
很骚  很性感
Very hot. Very sexy.
但是太国际化了  她不会跑来美国的
But she's too international. She's never gonna be around.
-所以呢  -所以你得把握胜算
-So? -So you gotta play the odds.
挑个一直会待在国内的人
Pick somebody who's gonna be in the country like all the time.
是啊  你之所以钓不到
Yeah. Because that's why
伊莎贝拉·罗塞里尼是因为地理因素
you won't get lsabella Rossellini. Geography.
原来你说的"烧"是真的烧啊
Okay. So by "melting" you meant melting.
这算艺术品吗
So is it,like, art?
要烧艺术品也可以
Yeah, you can melt art.
可以借个电话用吗
Hey,can I use your phone?
当然  你要打给你妈
Yeah, sure. You want to call your mom?
不  我想拿来烧
No, I wanna melt it.
那现在不行
Oh. Well, not right now.
我要去睡了
You know what I think, I'm just gonna go to bed.
烟熏得我头痛
The fumes are giving me a headache. So...
晚安  老弟
Good night,"bro."
晚安
Good night.
拿着
Here.
以防万一
You know, just in case.
太好了
Oh, excellent!
-那是什么空手道  -什么都不是
- What kind of karate is that? - No kind.
那是他自创的
He just makes it up.
-你们处得怎样  -挺烂的
- How's it going with you guys? - So far it kind of blows.
我以为他会有弟弟的感觉
I don't know, I just thought he'd feel more like a brother.
就像你和罗斯  亲密融洽
Like you and Ross. Just like close and connected and....
现在是很亲  但是以前
Oh honey, We're close now. You wouldn't believe the years...
我们又吵又打
of nugies, and wedgies, and flying wedgies,
又拉又扯
and atomic wedgies and....
然后裙子就会被扯到头上去
That's when the waistband actually goes over your head.
我们还学舌去烦对方
Oh, we used to drive each other crazy playing the shadow game.
学舌游戏怎么玩的
Oh, how do you play the shadow game?
-我在问你啊  -我在问你啊
- I just asked you. - I just asked you.
我没空跟你闹
I don't have time for this.
-就是这么玩的  -你这么快就放弃了
- No, that is what the game is. - You just gave up really quickly.
-有看到乔伊吗  -怎么了
- Have you seen Joey? - What's the matter?
就是这个
Oh, just this!
其实是我不好
You know what, it's my fault, really,
沙发就是用来放涂料的
because the couch is where we usually keep the varnish.
把瓷砖拿给我
Somebody wanna hand me one of those tiles?
-怎么回事  -他在帮我重铺地板
- What's going on? - He's retiling my floor.
泥水匠
You, spackle boy!
-给我起来  -你要有始有终
- Get up! - Ah, now you started this, you'll finish it!
他先糟蹋我那的好吗
He started mine first!
灰姑娘去钉柜子  灰姑娘去铺瓷砖
Build the unit, Cinderellie. Lay the tile, Cinderellie
大章鱼
Big octopus.
是啊
Yeah.
你好  天哪  我都忘了
Hello. Oh, my God! I totally forgot!
不能找别人吗
Well, can't someone else do it?
但是我有客人
But I have company.
没关系  我去
Yeah, no no, that's all right. I'll come in, okay.
弗兰克对不起  我得去工作了
Frank, I'm really sorry, but I have to be going to work.
我的一个熟客坚持要我做
It's one of my regulars and he's insisting that I do him.
你在做什么工作
Hey, what kind of work do you do?
我是按摩师
I'm a masseuse.
我帮客人按摩什么的
I give people massages and stuff.
你在那种按摩院工作
You work at one of those massage parlors?
我们不那样叫  不过没错
Well, you know, we don't call it that. But, yeah.
好劲爆
That's wild.
我完全不知道
No, I had no idea.
好吧
Alrighty.
我过一会儿就回来
I'll be back in a little bit.
除非你想跟我去
Unless you want to come with me.
你是说  围观吗
You mean, like, watch?
不  你也可以找个人按摩  免费招待
No. No, you can get one yourself. It'll be on the house.
不然要姐姐干嘛
You know, what are big sisters for?
知道吗  我还没考虑过这问题
Well, I don't think this. You know?
不  我不会亲自招呼你
No. No, no. I wouldn't do you myself.
那样很奇怪
I mean, that would be weird.
我会请其他小姐来做
Yeah, I'll get one of the other girls to do it.
很好玩的
This is so much fun!
-激动吗  -绝对的
- Hey! Are you excited? - Yeah.
莫妮卡和瑞秋也在那工作吗
Hey, do Monica and Rachel work there?
好漂亮
It's beautiful!
之前的地板好像一场噩梦
It's like the first bathroom floor there ever was!
你想进去干嘛
Whoa! What are you going in there for?
还要拿号吗
You want, like, a number?
-你好  -再见
- Hello. - Hi. Bye.
好的  我选好了
Okay. I'm done with my choices.
这是最后的名单
These are final.
-来的正是时候啊  -对啊  好正式啊
- Well, it's about time. -Yeah. Very official.
没错  钱德勒用他的电脑印的
Oh, yeah. Well, you know, Chandler printed it up on his computer.
这压膜是谁做的
And who laminated it?
我咯
That was me.
拿来我看看
All right, let me see.
乌玛·舒曼  薇诺·娜瑞德
"Uma Thurman, Winona Ryder,
伊莉莎白·赫莉
Elizabeth Hurley...
蜜雪儿·菲佛
Michelle Pfeiffer...
桃乐丝·汉弥尔[溜冰名将]
Dorothy Hammel"?
这是我的名单
Hey, it's my list!
宝贝  你知道她只有在冰上才会那样转吧
Okay, honey. You do realize she only spins like that on ice?
-怎么了  -她扭断了我的手
- What's going on? - She broke my arm!
-他摸我的屁股  -是她先摸我的
- He touched my fanny. - No, she touched mine first!
那是我的工作
That's my job!
那是什么意思
So wait, what's the deal?
我可以上你  但不能摸你
I can have sex with you but I can't touch you?
-你不能上她  -你以为我是妓女吗
- You can't have sex with her! - What'd you think I was a hooker?
不  我知道你是按摩师
No, okay. I know. You're a masseuse.
这很好  我又不是警察
It's cool. I'm not a cop!
贾思敏  你去让威佛先生
Okay, Jasmine, can you ask Mr. Wiffler
等5分钟好吗
if he can wait for five minutes.
好
Fine.
我不喜欢你
I don't like you.
你以为我是干那行的  天哪
So that's what you thought I did? God!
我不是干那行的
That's not what I do!
你不是干那行的
Wait, what that's not what you do?
不是
No!
你怎么会这么想
Why would you think that?
不知道  这里是纽约嘛  我只是...
I don't know. I mean, you know this is the city, you know? I just....
我是说...
I mean...
我不知道
I don't know.
管不了了  好一个完美的周末完美的句点
Whatever. It's the perfect end to the perfect weekend anyway.
等等
Oh, wait.
你说得没错  确实很完美
No, you're right. No, it was perfect.
我居然把它搞砸了
I can't believe that I screwed it up so bad.
你觉得很完美
You thought it was perfect?
也许称不上完美
Well, no, maybe it wasn't perfect...
但却很酷
but you know, it was pretty cool, you know?
我们聊得很愉快
Because we had all those great talks, you know?
你觉得哪一次特别愉快
Which ones in particular were great for you?
就是卷舌头的事
Well, you know, about the tongue thing, you know?
还有告诉你我喜欢什么  讨厌什么
And how I told you about my likes and my dislikes.
我喜欢烧东西  不喜欢不能烧的东西
How I like to melt stuff, and how I dislike stuff that doesn't melt.
对  好吧
Right. Okay.
我觉得可以对你畅所欲言
Yeah, you know, 'cause I feel like I can really talk to you
因为你是我姐姐
because you're my sister, you know?
是那样  我想没错
Yeah. I guess I do, yeah.
结果我却摸你朋友  惹你生气
And then I go feel your friend up and make you mad at me.
我也没有气到跳脚
Well, I wasn't hopping mad, you know?
你跳了一两下
You hopped a little bit.
我真的很抱歉  真心的
Yeah, I'm really sorry. You know, I'm really...
算了
Okay.
我觉得现在这是本周末最棒的时刻
Well, this is my favorite part of the weekend. Right now. This.
现在
This?
拜托  我们去了时代广场
Oh, come on. We went to, we went to Times Square.
买到了忍者娃娃  我差点被妓女扭断手
We found ninja stars. I almost get my arm broken by a hooker.
她不是妓女
She's not a hooker.
我跟朋友吹牛时  她就是
When I tell my friends about her, she will be.
数到三
Okay, on 3!
一  二
1,2
为什么不直接数到二
Why don't we just go on 2?
为什么要数到二
Why 2?
这样比较快
Because it's faster.
要不是你啰哩叭嗦
Yeah, I could've counted to 3
早就数到三了
like four times without all the "2" talk.
-好吧  但是以后...  -好了  够了
- All right, but in the future... - OK, Come on!
这个柜子很重的好吗
Heavy thing! Not getting lighter!
一  二
Okay, 1, 2
所以要数到二吗
So we are going with two?
乔伊  干得好
Oh, good job, Joe.
好大
It's big.
是啊  大得连我的门都看不见了
Yeah-yeah, so big that it actually makes our doors look smaller!
可能是我的尺子有问题
Maybe my ruler's wrong.
可能所有尺子都有问题
Maybe all the rulers are wrong.
其实还好嘛
It's not that bad.
你的挡一点 我的挡一点
So what, it blocks a little of your door, a little of my door.
我有个更好的主意
Yeah. You know what, I got a better idea.
干脆不要挡我的门  都去挡你的
How about it blocks none of my door, and a lot of your door?
先说一声  那边的油漆还没干
Listen, before I forget, that side is still wet.
我跟你确认一下
Okay sir, let me just see if I've got this right.
是咖啡因减半  中大杯  少许榛果糖浆
So this is a half-caf, double-tall, easy hazelnut...
无脂无沫  加热的咖啡对吧
nonfat, no foam, with whip, extra-hot latte, right?
太好了
Okay. Great.
变态
You freak.
谢谢
Thank you.
一杯咖啡外带
A coffee to go, please.
是伊莎贝拉·罗塞里尼
Isabella Rossellini!
不会吧  天哪
Are you serious? Oh, my God!
该死  我居然把她删掉了
Damn! I cannot believe I took her off my list!
怎么  否则你会行动吗
Why? Because otherwise you'd go for it?
搞不好
Yeah, maybe.
骗人
You lie.
你觉得我不会跟她搭讪
You don't think I'd go up to her?
你花了十年才承认你喜欢我
It took you 10 years to finally admit you liked me.
是吗  你最好庆幸这份名单已经压膜了
Yeah? Well, missy, you better be glad that list is laminated.
这样吧  你放马过去  就当她是候补人选
You know what, honey? You go ahead. We'll call her an alternate.
-好的  拿着我的饼  -好的
- OK, hold my cruller. - Okay.
瑞秋  你真的要让他去
Rachel, are you really gonna let him do this?
亲爱的  他可是要去泡伊莎贝拉·罗塞里尼啊
Honey, he's about to go hit on lsabella Rossellini.
可惜这没有爆米花
I'm just sorry we don't got popcorn.
你好  我是罗斯
Hi, I'm Ross.
你不认识我  但我是你的超级粉丝
You don't know me, but I'm a big, big fan of yours.
我是说...
I mean...
《蓝丝绒》
Blue Velvet.
我能不能请你喝一杯咖啡
Oh, I was wondering if I could maybe buy you a uh, a cup of coffee.
或是这杯咖啡算我的
Or reimburse you for that one.
你不是跟那个女生一对
Aren't you with that girl over there?
算是啦
Well, yeah, kind of.
但是没关系  我们达过共识
But that's okay, see we have an understanding.
我们都有一份五人明星录
See we each have this list of five famous people,
你在我的名单上
and you were one of mine.
所以我可以跟你上床
So I'm allowed to sleep with you.
这是恭维
No, no, no, it's flattering.
是嘛
I don't know
等一下嘛  伊莎贝拉
Wait. Wait, Isabella.
先别急着否决
Don't just dismiss this so fast.
这可是千载难逢的机会
I mean, this is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
对你而言没错
Yeah, for you.
这就是名单
Is that the list?
-没错  -我可以看吗?
- Oh yes. - May I see it?
不行
Ah, No.
-看看嘛  -好吧
-Come on. -But Okay.
我不在名单上
I'm not in the list!
这不是定稿
See, but that's not the final draft.
都压膜了
It's laminated.
好吧  你本来在我名单上的
Yeah, okay, see, you were on my list.
但是我的朋友钱德勒...
But then my friend, Chandler...
他觉得你太国际化了
brought up the good point that you are international.
所以我拿薇诺娜·瑞德取代了你  比较本土
So I bumped you for Winona Ryder. Local.
真是太讽刺了  因为我也有一份名单
You know, it's ironic, because I have a list...
列了五个咖啡店蠢货
...of five goofy coffeehouse guys.
就在昨天  那个人取代了你
And yesterday, I just bumped you for that guy over there.
当朋友就好了
We're just gonna be friends.
你知道吗
You know what?
我赌我能塞到那里面去
I bet you I could fit in there.
5块钱赌你塞不进去
I've got five bucks says you can't.
掏支票吧  先生
Get out your checkbook, mister.
我有现金
Oh, I think I have the cash.
你太逊了
You are dogged, man!
我塞得刚刚好
I totally fit!
是啊  你赢了
Yeah. You got me.
我输了5元大钞
I'm out five big ones.
拿去吧
There you go.
谢谢
Thank you.
总统先生  你好
Oh, well, hello, Mr. Lincoln!
祝你下次好运
Better luck next time, buddy!
酒钱我来出
And the drinks are on me!